Hi guys, and welcome to this Python refresher.
In this section we're going to learn about all of the main features of Python
features of Python, that you might need for this course.
As such, it's a bit of a long section.
So, there's a couple of things you can do in order to speed through it faster.
This is what you'll see when you are in the course
and you can see on the right you've got all of your lectures.
If you know the contents of any one lecture,
for example, you already know about string formatting in Python,
then you can skip that video entirely.
And, if you want to mark it as complete, you can do so by just clicking on this little box there.
I do recommend that if you speed through the videos, you have a look at a couple of points
throughout the video to make sure that you do know everything that's covered.
In addition, something else you can use to go through these videos faster,
is the "Speed Playback Rate" in the Udemy Player.
If you think I'm speaking too slowly, or you just want to go quickly through the videos, you can always click on it
and change the speed setting.
As long as you can understand me, you'll be okay.
Thank you for joining me again in this course. I hope you'll enjoy it.
I'll see you in the next video!